Guide to the Hanna House Collection SC0280
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Hanna, Paul R. files on Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1982-1992; Accession ARCH-1997-189
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art: correspondence re loan (and reproduction) of Frank Lloyd Wright chairs (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Documentation of work done on house, pre-1989; Accession ARCH-2004-237
  - J. Hanna drawing, signed by FLW, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Summary of work done (Box 2)
  - Drawings-Driveway and retaining wall (Box 3)
- Photograph album-Nissan Motor Corporation visit, 1977-03-01; Accession ARCH-2008-247 (Box 1)
- Photographs, Accession ARCH-2010-092
  - 3-ring binder containing b/w photographs of the interior and exterior of the house, along with several color images mostly showing brick damage, 1995 Jan (Box 1)
  - 30 b/w photographs of furniture (chairs and ottoman) designed for the house [origin of these images is not noted on prints] (Box 1)
  - 30 b/w negatives of furniture (chairs and ottoman) (Box 1)
  - Color transparencies of furniture (chairs and ottoman) (Box 1)
  - Digital images of family scrapbook [still in family's possession], 21 computer file(s) (tiff)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-188
  - "House Beautiful" Magazine, 1963 Jan (Box 1)
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2017-284
  - Photographs and negatives (Box 1)